[Music]
In another video of Gyan and in today's
video we are going to talk
about ICICI Bank stock. It
closed up by almost 2% in the Friday session
and today about 3 hours ago the
company posted the results of its Daughter-2. We will
discuss about those results. The
action that we got
to see on Friday, will it continue on Monday,
we will talk about it now. If you guys are new to the channel, then
you should also subscribe to the channel
so that you can get daily videos.
What comes next is that on Thursday the
results of Axis Bank came and
about 70% profit was shown in Axis Bank.
Now Axis Bank being that too a
private sector bank, ICICI Bank is a
private sector bank, so the
street is expecting very good results
and the results are quite good, you too, to be
honest, if we talk about profit, there is an
up profit of about 37%.
Along with this, this profit is
after provisioning, so provisions  Meaning it has been
reduced this time only. Compared to last
ported provisions, basically it means
that the NPS, which are bad loans, are
written off. This
means that the bank already catches the loss on them. The bank
then shows the profit. So
if the provisions increase too much,
it means that the
health of the loan book of the bank is not good.
But here it is being seen that the
bank has reduced the provisions for pot and quarter.
This means that the quality of loans
given by the banks, the companies to which the banks
gave loans are good companies, they have a good
background and they are making timely
payments. Let's talk about the other
numbers in the results post,
as I told you, a
profit rise of 37% was seen
in last September and
if you see in this September, there was a profit of ₹5500 crore
in last September. In this September,
they made a profit of ₹757 crore in D
quadrant in September.
If you see then  An update of Rs 14787 crore has been
seen in UP, there
is a rise of 26.5% again in earning year date interest
income, I also explained in my previous video that it is a
basic thing, so the
bank gives a loan and also gets your HD
done, so firstly it charges interest
to its customer and it
collects interest from the market on which
it has given loans, for example,
if the bank is giving you 6% interest on your
FB and on top of that the
bank is giving loan at 9% interest, then the 3% that is
left is the net interest income of a bank,
so this is what we are talking about, if
you look at Sagar year, then an update of 26% has been
seen in it, now there are two-three
interesting things in it, if
we see then advance net advance means that a
loan is given for a particular amount of time, the company
calls it advance, so the advance
advance has been reduced by 2.2%,
so 22 sorry  22 basis points three has
come at 3.1 3.19% q1q and net 10 PM
Modi has come at 0.6, this 0.61 and 3.19%
is the cross advance, its MP together
NP is different, so this thing has come out that the bank has got
a good number in its results
because if you read the complete statement of the bank, then it has been
said in the bank that
loans worth about Rs 1100 crore have been
declared NPA, within this, the
bank has still promoted the provisions a lot, but if you compare it
with the last quarter, then it is confirmed that this is the thing
which is different in it, if we
look at the results of IDBI Bank as I told in my last video, the provisions in it are big, in this the
provisions in it are of the last quarter, so
this is a good thing, now if we
talk about this, this is the broad thing about its banker results,
after provisions, we talked about net
interest, if  If we
look at ICICI Bank on the charts, the interesting thing is that this
week's move was quite good, but if you
look at the daily charts, I still
think that the trend is largely
neutral and the reason for this is that the
upward resistance of around 940 is a
very big resistance for ICICI Bank.
Now the question is what will happen on Monday? I think there is bull
trading on Monday and a big
session will come on Tuesday. But still,
you will definitely see the impact of today's result.
But the reaction that we saw in Axis Bank,
where the price moved from ₹800 to ₹900
within a single day, there is no reason behind it,
so those are much better numbers than expected.
So, whenever you
see any update after the result, it
depends only on what the
expectations are.
How were the positions formed before that, that is within the stock,
not in the market.  On the matter whether the
results are good or bad, it will be a
thing to be seen and the big region which
I told you is that if 94 crosses 940, then
ICICI Bank can then move towards 1000 also
but I have a little doubt in it because the
results of Axis Bank are not good, the results are good
but the stock has already moved a lot, if
we talk about this year only, then
in 2022 the stock has already moved from almost 650 till now till
9:30, so
ICICI Bank has already shown you a good move of 50%,
so I would only look at the
determinants, if it crosses 940 then
India has also done the
rest, let's see the action,
definitely put it in the comment section, I will meet
you in my next video, till then take care of yourself